A Guide to the Photographs of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1989-1993
Library of Virginia
- 91-0171, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Scoliosis Awareness Month, 2/26/1991 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- 91-0172, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Victory Award and presented a pin, 2/26/1991 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- 91-0173, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Youth Art Month and is presented a flag, 2/26/1991 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- 91-0174, Photo of Secretary Elizabeth Haskell, Secretary of Natural Resources, 2/27/1991 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- 91-0402, Gov. Wilder signs COFR for keep Va Beautiful Week, 3/7/1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- 91-0403, Gov. Wilder meets with several of the Governor's Interns, 3/7/1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- 91-0404, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Flunkbusters, 3/7/1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- 91-0405, Gov. Wilder gives trophies for Gov. Sport Awards for Volleyball, 3/12/1991 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- 91-0406, Gov. Wilder visits with Arch-deacon Photolo of the Episcopal Diocese of South Africa, 3/12/1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- 91-0407, Portrait of Secretary Elizabeth Haskell, Secretary of Natural Resources, 3/13/1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- 91-0408, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Volunteer Rescue Squad Week, 3/14/1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- 91-0409, Gov. Wilder holds Open House at Roanoke City Hall, 3/16/1991 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- 91-0410, Gov. Wilder holds Open House at Roanoke City Hall, 3/16/1991 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- 91-0411, Gov. Wilder holds Open House at Roanoke City Hall, 3/16/1991 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- 91-0412, Gov. Wilder holds Open House at Roanoke City Hall, 3/16/1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- 91-0415, Gov. Wilder is presented a forfeiture check by the Federal, 3/18/1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- 91-0416, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for National Auctioneer's Week, 3/30/1991 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- 91-0417, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Downtown Development Week, 3/20/1991 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- 91-0418, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for America Home Week, 3/20/1991 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- 91-0419, Gov. Wilder presents a certificate to Kevin Westley, 3/21/1991 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- 91-0420, Gov. Wilder visits with councilmen John Ray and friend, also photo with pin, 3/22/1991 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- 91-0421, Gov. Wilder speaks to Delegate Cooper, Mr. Maxey, Debra Maxey, and Josh about Deficit disorder, 3/25/1991 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- 91-0422, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Paraprofessional Week, 3/27/1991 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- 91-0423, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Virginia Society for Medical Technology, 3/27/1991 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- 91-0424, Gov. Wilder presents Cultural Relation Fellowship Awards, 3/29/1991 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- 91-0425, Gov. Wilder presents Cultural Relation Fellowship Awards, 3/29/1991 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- 91-0426, Mr. Stephen Smith and family visits Gov. Wilder, 3/29/1991 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- 91-0427, Gov. Wilder signs HB 1429 Firearms Transfer Criminal History Check, 4/3/1991 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- 91-0428, Gov. Wilder signs HB 2011-2012 Regulation of Limousines and Certification of Self Insurance, 4/3/1991 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- 91-0429, Gov. Wilder signs HB 1321 Firearms Transfer Criminal History Check, 4/3/1991 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- 91-0430, Gov. Wilder signs HB 1153 Equal Housing, 4/3/1991 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- 91-0431, Gov. Wilder signs HB 1019 Court Fee charged to Drug Offenders, 4/1/1991 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- 91-0432, Gov. Wilder signs SB 505 Exempt certain organizations from property taxation, 4/1/1991 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- 91-0433, Gov. Wilder signs HB 1280 Contractual provisions, 4/1/1991 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- 91-0434, Gov. Wilder signs HB 1308 Delegate Woodrum, 4/1/1991 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- 91-0435, Gov. Wilder signs HB 1251 Incorporation Community of Castlewood in Russell County as a town, 4/1/1991 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- 91-0436, Gov. Wilder signs SB-685 Senator Stallings, 4/1/1991 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- 91-0437, Gov. Wilder signs HB-1402 Authority for licensed Nurse Practitioner, 4/2/1991 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- 91-0438, Gov. Wilder signs HB-1786 Delegate Quillen, 4/2/1991 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- 91-0439, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for Child Abuse Prevention Month, 4/4/1991 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- 91-0440, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for Hospital Pharmacy Week, 4/9/1991 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- 91-0441, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for National Science and Technology Education Week, 4/9/1991 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- 91-0442, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for National Organ and Tissue Donor Awareness Week, 4/9/1991 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- 91-0443, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for REACT Month, 4/9/1991 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- 91-0444, Gov. Wilder speaks at Bill of Rights Bicentennial celebration at Gunston Hall Home of George Mason, 4/14/1991 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- 91-0445, Gov. Wilder speaks at Bill of Rights Bicentennial celebration at Gunston Hall Home of George Mason, 4/14/1991 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- 91-0446, Gov. Wilder visits with Ms. Sauitri Belizairi, 4/16/1991 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- 91-0447, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for Loyalty Day, 4/16/1991 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- 91-0448, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for Older Virginians Month, 4/16/1991 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- 91-0449, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for 1991 Law Day, 4/16/1991 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- 91-0450, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for National Nursing Home Week, 4/16/1991 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- 91-0451, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for National Safe Boating Week, 4/16/1991 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- 91-0452, Gov. Wilder visits with a group of Australians Home Business Women, 4/16/1991 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- 91-0453, Flags on State Capital at Half Staff, 4/16/1991 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- 91-0454, Ladies from Hadassah presents a certificate to Gov. Wilder, 4/16/1991 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- 91-0455, Ladies from Hadassah presents a certificate to Gov. Wilder, 4/16/1991 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- 91-0456, Gov. Wilder kicks off the Heroes program with Arthur Ashe at Mosby Elementary School, 4/18/1991 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- 91-0457, Gov. Wilder visits with Ch-ETA Pi group of ladies, 4/18/1991 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- 91-0458, Gov. Wilder views new drug Free School zone sign, 4/18/1991 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- 91-0459, Gov. Wilder is presented a check from Housing Partnership, 4/18/1991 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- 91-0460, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for Nurse Anesthetist Week, 4/18/1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- 91-0461, Gov. Wilder holds Open House at Danville Municipal Building Danville, Virginia, 4/20/1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- 91-0462, Gov. Wilder holds Open House at Danville Municipal Building Danville, Virginia, 4/20/1991 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- 91-0463, Gov. Wilder holds Open House at Danville Municipal Building Danville, Virginia, 4/20/1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- 91-0464, Gov. Wilder holds Open House at Danville Municipal Building Danville, Virginia, 4/20/1991 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- 91-0465, Gov. Wilder holds Open House at Danville Municipal Building Danville, Virginia, 4/20/1991 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- 91-0466, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for Childhood Immunization Week, 4/22/1991 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- 91-0467, Gov. Wilder meets with students from Varnet School of Texas, 4/22/1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- 91-0468, Gov. Wilder does a interview with reporter from an African magazine, 4/23/1991 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- 91-0469, Gov. Wilder annual Waste Management Conference, 4/23/1991 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- 91-0470, Gov. Wilder presents Drug Free School zone, signs to Blackwell Elementary, 4/23/1991 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- 91-0471, Gov. Wilder present Certificate of Recognition for Outstanding Community Service and Ribbon Cutting at WTVR-TV Station, 4/23/1991 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- 91-0472, Gov. Wilder present Certificate of Recognition for Outstanding Community Service and Ribbon cutting at WTVR-TV Station, 4/23/1991 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- 91-0473, Gov. Wilder present Certificate of Recognition for Outstanding Community Service and Ribbon Cutting at WTVR-TV Station, 4/23/1991 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- 91-0474, Gov. Wilder meets with Minister of Trade from Malawi, 4/22/1991 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- 91-0475, Gov. Wilder meets with Col. Robert Suthard, Secretary of Public Safety and Staff, 4/24/1991 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- 91-0476, Gov. Wilder visits with Mr. Clay while making a courtesy call, 4/26/1991 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- 91-0477, Gov. Wilder present a plaque for Nurse of the Year, 4/26/1991 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- 91-0478, Gov. Wilder meets with Yoshie Hatano the Ambassador of the United Nations, 4/30/1991 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- 91-0479, Gov. Wilder signs bills HB 1478 Delegate Bill Moore, Jr., 4/30/1991 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- 91-0480, Gov. Wilder signs bills HB 1893 Delegate William C. Moore, Jr., 4/30/1991 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- 91-0481, Gov. Wilder signs bills SB 609, Senator Dan Bird, Jr., 4/30/1991 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- 91-0482, Gov. Wilder signs SB 697, Senator Edward Houck, 4/30/1991 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- 91-0483, Gov. Wilder signs bills HB relating to avoid stipulation construction contract, 4/30/1991 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- 91-0484, Gov. Wilder signs bills SB 777, Senator Elliot S. Schewer, 4/30/1991 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- 91-0485, Gov. Wilder signs bills HB 1588, Delegate Jay W. DeBoer, 4/30/1991 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- 91-0486, Gov. Wilder signs bills SB 834 and HB 1891, Senator Robert Scott and Delegate E. Eck, 4/30/1991 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- 91-0487, Gov. Wilder meets with the Press in the Conference room, 4/30/1991 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- 91-0488, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for Professional Secretary Week, 5/2/1991 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- 91-0489, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for Good will Industries Week, 5/2/1991 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- 91-0490, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Historic Preservation Week, 5/2/1991 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- 91-0492, Gov. Wilder presented the accreditation certificate for Games and Inland Fisheries, 5/9/1991 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- 91-0493, Gov. Wilder visits with Mr. And Mrs. Jon Mass and their two children, 5/13/1991 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- 91-0494, Passport photo of Laura F. Dillard Gov.'s Press Secretary, 5/14/1991 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- 91-0495, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for National Employee Health and Fitness Week, 5/15/1991 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- 91-0496, Gov. Wilder visits with students from Caprom Elementary School 4th grade, 5/15/1991 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- 91-0497, Gov. Wilder meets with Chinese student journalist, 5/16/1991 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- 91-0498, Gov. Wilder visits with AAA Poster Contest Winners, 5/16/1991 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- 91-0499, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Alcohol and Drug related Birth Defects, 5/16/1991 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- 91-0755, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Foster Care Month, 5/15/1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- 91-0756, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Nursing Home Week, 5/16/1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- 91-0757, Gov. Wilder meets with students from St. Peter Claver School, New York, 5/19/1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- 91-0758, Gov. Wilder meets with Elena Grambanic Miss Jr. America Pageant Contestant, 5/21/1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- 91-0759, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for May is Egg Month in Virginia, 5/21/1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- 91-0760, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Baltic Freedom Day, 5/21/1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- 91-0761, The president of Standard Drug Company present plaque to the state, 5/22/1991 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- 91-0762, Gov. Wilder present certificate to winners for Drug-Free School Award, 5/28/1991 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- 91-0763, Gov. Wilder presents a plaque to Gayton School students for smoke-free class of 2000, 5/28/1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- 91-0764, Gov. Wilder with Mr. Wayne Shock Director of Department of Deaf and Hard of Hearing, 5/29/1991 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- 91-0765, Gov. Wilder visits with Delegation from Poland's Employment Office, 5/29/1991 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- 91-0766, Gov. Wilder unveils New Drug Program for the Commonwealth, l for parents and children, 5/30/1991 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- 91-0767, Gov. Wilder unveils New Drug Program for the Commonwealth, l for parents and children, 5/30/1991 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- 91-0768, Gov. Wilder unveils New Drug Program for the Commonwealth, l for parents and children, 5/30/1991 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- 91-0769, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for American Tree Farm System, 6/17/1991 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- 91-0770, Gov. Wilder answers questions for Urban Journalism Workshop students, 6/17/1991 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- 91-0771, Gov. Wilder chairs the Annual Virginia Military Conference, 6/17/1991 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- 91-0772, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Heartburn Disease Awareness Month, 6/20/1991 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- 91-0773, Gov. Wilder receives a certificate that was presented to Department of Corrections, 6/20/1991 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- 91-0774, Gov. Wilder stands with the Board of Volunteerism, 6/20/1991 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- 91-0775, Gov. wilder talks with Mr. Wayne Shook, Director of the Department for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing, 6/20/1991 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- 91-0776, Gov. Wilder talks with students from the Hampton Roads area High Schools, 6/20/1991 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- 91-0777, Gov. Wilder visits with Israeli Boys and Girls Scout while on a caravan through the U.S., 6/21/1991 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- 91-0778, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Mr. Ray Vaughan upon his retirement, 6/21/1991 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- 91-0779, Gov. Wilder holds another Open House this was held on the eastern shore, 6/22/1991 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- 91-0780, Gov. Wilder holds another Open House this was held on the eastern shore, 6/22/1991 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- 91-0781, Gov. Wilder holds another Open House this was held on the eastern shore, 6/22/1991 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- 91-0782, Gov. Wilder holds another Open House this was held on the eastern shore, 6/22/1991 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- 91-0783, Gov. Wilder attends a staff picnic over on eastern shore, 6/22/1991 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- 91-0784, Gov. Wilder attends a staff picnic over on eastern shore, 6/22/1991 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- 91-0785, Gov. Wilder receives a courtesy call from Mr. Goodman, 6/24/1991 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- 91-0786, Gov. Wilder receives a courtesy call from Mr. Jim Tso, 6/24/1991 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- 91-0787, Gov. Wilder visits with Ambassador Afanda from the nation of Kenya, 6/25/1991 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- 91-0788, Gov. Wilder visits with Ambassador Afanda from the nation of Kenya, 6/25/1991 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- 91-0789, Gov. Wilder visits with Delegation from Angola, 6/25/1991 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- 91-0790, Secretary of Administration meets with Delegation from the country of Angola, 6/28/1991 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- 91-0791, Gov. Wilder Charitable Campaign State Representative, 7/8/1991 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- 91-0792, Gov. Wilder visits with General Franz F. Lanz Commander German forces for NATO in the U.S., 7/8/1991 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- 91-0793, Gov. Wilder meets with Miss Melinda DeFiesta, Miss American Coed and her family, 7/8/1991 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- 91-0794, Gov. Wilder meets with Miss Stephanie Muskovac, Miss American Pre-Teen ans her mother, 7/8/1991 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- 91-0795, Mr. Frank Parren a member of the EPU passport photos, 7/8/1991 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- 91-0796, Gov. Wilder holds a dinner for the Gov.'s Fellows at the Executive Mansion, 7/8/1991 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- 91-0797, Gov. Wilder holds a dinner for the Gov.'s Fellows at the Executive Mansion, 7/8/1991 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- 91-0798, Gov. Wilder holds a press conference to announce the State of Virginia Drug Program, 7/11/1991 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- 91-01, Passport photos Leslie McAlexander, 7/12/1991 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- 91-0799, Gov. wilder posed with DGS Painters, 7/12/1991 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- 91-0800, Gov. Wilder talks with Mr. Meredith Bulleton while making a courtesy call, 7/12/1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- 91-0802, Gov. Wilder presents letters of Appreciation to the Gov. Fellow's who worked in the Gov.'s Office, 7/25/1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- 91-0803, Gov. wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Tidewater Psychiatric Int. Week, 7/25/1991 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- 91-0804, Gov. Wilder presents certificate to the Country and Town of Wise, 7/25/1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- 91-0805, Gov. Wilder talks with students who are part of MVC Gov.'s School, 7/25/1991 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- 91-0806, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Park and Recreation Month, 7/25/1991 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- 91-0808, Mr. Michael Braxton and family, American Embassy Warshaw makes a courtesy call, 7/25/1991 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- 91-0809, Miss Cheryl Watkins makes a courtesy call on Gov. Wilder, 7/25/1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- 91-0810, Gov. Wilder visits with students from south West Virginia part of the Gov.'s School of Science and Technology, 7/29/1991 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- 91-0811, Mr. Randy Rollin, Assistant Secretary for Public Safety, 7/31/1991 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- 91-0812, Mr. Theo Twitty, Assistant Secretary for Public Safety, 7/31/1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- 91-0813, Virginia Port Authority presents a globe to Gov. Wilder, 8/1/1991 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- 91-0814, Mr. Clarence Hayin presents a painting to Gov. Wilder, 8/1/1991 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- 91-0815, Virginia Community College system presents a tapestry to Gov. Wilder, 8/1/1991 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- 91-0816, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for and presents a National Environment Award, 8/1/1991 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- 91-0817, Russian Delegation meets with staff of the Gov.'s Office and Attorney General's Staff as well as Supreme Court Justice, 8/2/1991 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- 91-0818, Russian Delegation meets with staff of the Gov.'s Office and Attorney General's Staff as well as Supreme Court Justice, 8/2/1991 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- 91-0820, Gov. Wilder presents trophies for the Gov.'s softball and volleyball league, 8/5/1991 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- 91-0821, Gov. Wilder visits with Ms. Janice Maning, Miss Virginia American Teen and her parents, 8/5/1991 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- 91-0822, Gov. Wilder talks with Major General Wallace Arnold and presents a gift, 8/5/1991 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- 91-0823, Ms. Beth Porter and family visits with Gov. Wilder, 8/9/1991 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- 91-0824, Gov. wilder visits Virginia Favorite Pre-teen #91 Elizabeth Codejoe and family, 8/14/1991 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- 91-0825, Gov. Wilder talks with the Chesapeake Commissioner of Revenue- Ray Conner, 8/14/1991 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- 91-0826, Gov. Wilder receives the preliminary report of the comptroller and receives a plaque that was presented to the state, 8/14/1991 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- 91-0827, Gov. Wilder talks over a script with people while they are doing a PSA, 8/14/1991 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- 91-0828, Staff photo of the policy office, 8/14/1991 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- 91-0829, Gov. Wilder talks with a group of young adults about problems within their age group, 8/16/1991 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- 91-0830, Gov. Wilder address a group from our children's Foundation and receive a plaque, 8/16/1991 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- 91-0831, Gov. Wilder is visited by Senator Julian Bond, family and friends, 8/19/1991 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- 91-0832, Gov. Wilder presents Virginia Baton twirling trophy to Miss Beth Brooks, 8/20/1991 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- 91-0833, Gov. Wilder visits with Miss Virginia American Princess Mariah Johnson and her mother, undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
- 91-0834, Gov. Wilder meets with citizens from Newport News at Open House held at Christopher Newport, 8/24/1991 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- 91-0835, Gov. Wilder meets with citizens from Newport News at Open House held at Christopher Newport, 8/24/1991 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- 91-0836, Gov. Wilder meets with citizens from Newport News at Open House held at Christopher Newport, 8/24/1991 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- 91-0837, Gov. Wilder meets with Secretary of Finance, Paul Timmerick and State treasurer, Eddie Moore, Jr., 8/23/1991 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- 91-0838, Gov. Wilder meets with Helmut Schaefer, Deputy Foreign Minister Germany, 8/26/1991 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- 91-0839, Attorney Mary Sue Terry addresses a group at New Town area of Richmond at New Home Building site, 8/27/1991 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- 91-0840, Attorney Mary Sue Terry addresses a group at New Town area of Richmond at New Home Building site, 8/27/1991 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- 91-0841, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Domestic Violence Awareness Month, 8/29/1991 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- 91-0842, Gov. Wilder meets with Miss Junior Virginia Pre-Teen, Erin Cahill and family, 8/29/1991 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- 91-0843, Gov. Wilder talks with church group from Washington, D.C. called the Pacesetter, 8/29/1991 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- 91-0844, Gov. Wilder meets with Ambassador McLean from New Zealand, 9/3/1991 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- 91-0845, Gov. Wilder meets with Intern Eastern European exchange program representative Miecqyslaw Czekanski, 9/6/1991 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- 91-0860, Gov. Wilder makes the announcement to run for the presidency of the U.S., 9/13/1991 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- 91-0861, Gov. Wilder makes the announcement to run for the presidency of the U.S., 9/13/1991 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- 91-0862, Gov. Wilder makes the announcement to run for the presidency of the U.S., 9/13/1991 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- 91-0873, Gov. Wilder meets with Tanzania Ambassador Charles Nyirabu, 9/24/1991 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- 91-0875, Gov. Wilder attends the opening ceremony of the of the signing of the Bill of Rights at the State Fair, 9/25/1991 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- 91-0876, Gov. Wilder attends the opening ceremony of the of the signing of the Bill of Rights at the State Fair, 9/25/1991 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- 91-0877, Secretary of the Commonwealth Pamela Womack swears in Lonnie Craig, 9/23/1991 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- 91-0878, Retirement party for Col. Tucker Major Lang and Lt. Harris of Capital Police, 9/29/1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- 91-0879, Retirement party for Col. Tucker Major Lang and Lt. Harris of Capital Police, 9/29/1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- 91-0880, Retirement party for Col. Tucker Major Lang and Lt. Harris of Capital Police, 9/29/1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- 91-0881, Speaker of the House A.L. Philpott of Henry Co. Memorial service held in the Rotunda of the State Capital, 9/30/1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- 91-0882, Speaker of the House A.L. Philpott of Henry Co. Memorial service held in the Rotunda of the State Capital, 9/30/1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- 91-0883, Speaker of the House A.L. Philpott of Henry Co. Memorial service held in the Rotunda of the State Capital, 9/30/1991 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- 91-0884, Gov. Wilder presents the first Drug Awareness Awards at the Luncheon, 10/16/1991 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- 91-0885, Gov. Wilder presents the first Drug Awareness Awards at the Luncheon, 10/16/1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- 91-0886, Gov. Wilder presents the first Drug Awareness Awards at the Luncheon, 10/16/1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- 91-0888, Gov. Wilder met with Miss Stacie Oppleman, Virginia Miss Teen 1991, 10/29/1991 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- 91-0889, Gov. Wilder Met with Gov. James Salen, Gov. of the Netherlands Antilles Island, 10/29/1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- 91-0893, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Child Health Week, 11/25/1991 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- 91-0894, Gov. Wilder accepts payment of taxes from the Pamunkey and Mattaponi Indian tribes, 11/26/1991 (Box 16, Folder 13)